china-proxy.org 2019-08-12

# China Proxy Privacy Policy

## China Proxy - Privacy Policy

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at [e-Mail](mailto:info@china-proxy.org)

At China-Proxy.org we consider the privacy of our visitors to be extremely important. This privacy policy document describes in detail the types of personal information is collected and recorded by China-Proxy.org and how we use it. 

**Log Files**  

China-proxy.org does not log user activity on this server. No logs are created or stored on this server.

China-proxy.org does not log IP addresses or websites visited via this Anonymizer since we have no use for this information.

**Visitor Counter**

China-proxy.org makes use of a simple visitor counter to gather statistics from the front page. These statistics contain general non-personal information about website visitors, such as web browser software, country, internet protocol address, screen resolution and operating system.

You are free to stop capture of your visit by our visitor counter. To do so, please follow this link and opt-out: <http://www.histats.com/optOut.php>

To understand how histats.com processes your data, please read its privacy policy: <http://www.histats.com/?act=5>

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
China-Proxy.org uses cookies to store information about visitors' preferences, to record user-specific information on which pages the site visitor accesses or visits, and to personalize or customize our web page content based upon visitors' browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
→ Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on China-proxy.org.  
→ Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our site's visitors based upon their visit to China-proxy.org and other sites on the Internet.   
→ Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - [http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html](https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html "Opt out of the Dart Cookie")

**Our Advertising Partners**

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include .......   

  * Google
  * PopAds
  * DoubleClick
  * PopMyAds

_While each of these advertising partners has their own Privacy Policy for their site_

You may follow this links to find the privacy policy for each of the advertising partners of China-Proxy.org.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology in their respective advertisements and links that appear on China-Proxy.org and which are sent directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by our site's third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on the site. 

China-Proxy.org has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

**Third Party Privacy Policies**  
You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. China-Proxy.org's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. You may find a comprehensive listing of these privacy policies above.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. [What Are Cookies?](https://www.whatarecookies.com/ "What Are Cookies")

**Children's Information**  
We believe it is important to provide added protection for children online. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children to observe, participate in and/or monitor and guide their online activity. China-Proxy.org does not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian believes that China-Proxy.org has in its database the personally-identifiable information of a child under the age of 13, please contact us immediately (using the contact in the first paragraph) and we will use our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records. 

**Online Privacy Policy Only**  
This privacy policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website and regarding information shared and/or collected there. This policy does not apply to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.

**Consent**  
By using our website, you hereby consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms. 

**Update**  
This Privacy Policy was last updated on: Thursday, May 24, 2018.

_Should we update, amend or make any changes to our privacy policy, those changes will be posted here._
